let question = [
    {
        number: 1,
        question: "What was the name of One Direction's debut album?",
        answer: "C. Up All Night",
        Options: [
            "A. Take Me Home",
            "B. Four",
            "C. Up All Night",
            "D. Midnight Memories"
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 2,
        question: "Which year did Westlife release their debut single 'Swear It Again'?",
        answer: "B. 1999",
        Options: [
            "A. 1979",
            "B. 1999",
            "C. 1989",
            "D. 2000"
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 3,
        question: "Which member of 5 Seconds of Summer plays the drums for the band?",
        answer: "D. Ashton Irwin",
        Options: [
            "A. Luke Hemmings",
            "B. Calum Hood",
            "C. Michael Clifford",
            "D. Ashton Irwin",

        ]
    },

    {
        number: 4,
        question: "Which member of One Direction released a solo album titled 'Mind of Mine' after the band's hiatus?",
        answer: "A. Zayn Malik",
        Options: [
            "A. Zayn Malik",
            "B. Harry Styles",
            "C. Louis Tomlinson",
            "D. Niall Horan"
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 5,
        question: "Who is the lead vocalist and guitarist of The Vamps?",
        answer: "C. Brad Simpson",
        Options: [
            "A. James McVey",
            "B. Joe Sugg",
            "C. Brad Simpson",
            "D. Connor Ball",
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 6,
        question: "Which member of BLACKPINK is known for her signature rap verses in their songs?",
        answer: "D. Jennie Kim.",
        Options: [
            "A. Jisoo Kim.",
            "B. Ros√© Park.",
            "C. Lisa Manoban.",
            "D. Jennie Kim.",
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 7,
        question: "Which member of Little Mix won the 2011 edition of the singing competition show 'The X Factor' as part of the group?",
        answer: "D. Perrie Edwards",
        Options: [
            "A. Jesy Nelson",
            "B. Jade Thirlwall",
            "C. Danielle Peazer",
            "D. Perrie Edwards",
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 8,
        question: "What is the name of ITZY's debut single that gained significant popularity upon its release in 2019?",
        answer: "A. Dalla Dalla",
        Options: [
            "A. Dalla Dalla",
            "B. Wannabe",
            "C. Not Shy",
            "D. Mafia in the Morning",
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 9,
        question: "Which member of Red Velvet is known for her unique and powerful vocal range, often showcased in their songs?",
        answer: "C. Wendy",
        Options: [
            "A. Irene",
            "B. Seulgi",
            "C. Wendy",
            "D. Yeri",
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 10,
        question: "Which reality TV show did Fifth Harmony first rise to fame on?",
        answer: "B. The X Factor USA",
        Options: [
            "A. American Idol",
            "B. The X Factor USA",
            "C. The X Factor UK",
            "D. America's Got Talent",
        ]
    }

];